In this video,
在这段视频中，
we're going to demonstrate the execution of code containing a whie loop.
我们将演示包含 whie 循环的代码的执行过程。
As always, we begin with the execution arrow at the start of main.
与往常一样，我们从 main 开头的执行箭头开始。
The first statement declares a variable x and
第一条语句声明变量 x，并
initializes it by calling g of 2 and 9.
通过调用 2 和 9 中的 g 对其进行初始化。
Inside of g, we declare the variable total and
在 g 中，我们声明变量 total
initialize it to 0, and then we reach a while loop.
并将其初始化为 0，然后我们到达 while 循环。
The conditional expression of this while loop is
这个 while 循环的条件表达式是
a less than b which in this case is 2 less than 9,
a 小于 b，在本例中为 2 小于 9，
which is true, so we enter the body of the while loop.
这是真的，所以我们输入 while 循环的主体。
The next statement is total plus equals a.
下一个语句是合计加等于 a。
Remember that this is shorthand for total equals total plus a, so
请记住，这是合计等于总和加 a 的简写，所以
total is going to equal 0 plus 2 which is 2.
总和将等于 0 加 2，即 2。
We assign 2 to total and now we have a printf statement.
我们将 2 分配给总数，现在我们有一个 printf 语句。
A = %d, b = %d new line,
A = %d，b = %d 新行，
where the first %d converts the value of a to a decimal number and
其中第一个 %d 将 a 的值转换为十进制数，
the second %d converts the value of b to a decimal number.
第二个 %d 将 b 的值转换为十进制数。
This prints out a = 2, b = 9.
这会打印出 a = 2，b = 9。
The next statement is a ++.
下一个语句是 ++。
Recall that this is shorthand for a = a + 1, so we're going to do a = 3.
回想一下，这是 a = a + 1 的简写，所以我们要做 a = 3。
B-- is shorthand for b = b- 1,
B--是 b = b-1 的简写，
so we're going to do b = 8.
所以我们要做 b = 8。
Now we've reached the close curly brace of the while loop, so
现在我们已经到达了 while 循环的
our execution arrow jumps right back up to the top of the while loop, right before
右大括号，所以我们的执行箭头会直接跳回到 while 循环的顶部，就在
the conditional expression to determine if we should enter the body of the loop.
条件表达式之前，以确定我们是否应该进入循环的主体。
Evaluating the conditional expression gives 3 less than 8 which is true,
计算条件表达式得出 3 小于 8，这是真的，
so we enter the body of the while loop again.
所以我们再次输入 while 循环的主体。
We do total +=a, 2+3 is 5,
我们总计 +=a，2+3 等于 5，
so we update total.
所以我们更新总数。
Then, we're going to print a=3, b=8.
然后，我们要打印 a=3，b=8。
We're going to increment a by 1 and decrement b by 1.
我们要将 a 递增 1，将 b 递减 1。
We reach the close curly brace at the bottom of the while loop again, so
我们再次到达了 while 循环底部的紧密卷曲支撑，所以
we jump back up to the top.
我们跳回了顶部。
4 less than 7 is true, so we enter the body of the while loop.
4 小于 7 是真的，所以我们进入了 while 循环的主体。
Total += a, printf a=4, b=7, increment a and
总计 += a，printf a=4，b=7，增量 a 和
decrement, jump back to the top of the loop.
减量，跳回循环的顶部。
5 less than 6 is true, so we enter the body of the while loop.
5 小于 6 是真的，所以我们进入了 while 循环的主体。
We execute each statement in the loop as before.
我们像以前一样执行循环中的每条语句。
Now, however, when we get back to the top of the loop and
但是，现在，当我们回到循环的顶部并
evaluate our conditional expression, we find 6 less that 5 is false.
评估我们的条件表达式时，我们发现少了 6，即 5 是假的。
Our execution arrow skips over the body of the loop and
我们的执行箭头跳过循环主体，
begins executing statements immediately after it.
紧接着开始执行语句。
The value of total to return is 14, so we return that to main
要返回的 total 值为 14，因此我们将其返回到 main
leaving function g and returning our execution arrow back in to main
离开函数 g，然后将执行箭头返回到 main，在
where we can now complete our initialization of x with x = 14.
那里我们现在可以在 x = 14 的情况下完成 x 的初始化。
We then continue executing statements in main.
然后，我们继续在 main 中执行语句。
We print out x = 14 and we return 0 exiting main and leaving the program.
我们打印出 x = 14 然后返回 0 退出 main 并离开程序。